[
  {
    "question_no.": 1,
    "Question": "What is the study of animals called?",
    "Option1": "Botany",
    "Option2": "Zoology",
    "Option3": "Geology",
    "Option4": "Astronomy",
    "Answer": "Zoology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 2,
    "Question": "Which class of animals is characterized by having a backbone?",
    "Option1": "Invertebrates",
    "Option2": "Vertebrates",
    "Option3": "Arthropods",
    "Option4": "Mollusks",
    "Answer": "Vertebrates"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 3,
    "Question": "What do you call an animal that eats only plants?",
    "Option1": "Carnivore",
    "Option2": "Omnivore",
    "Option3": "Herbivore",
    "Option4": "Detritivore",
    "Answer": "Herbivore"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 4,
    "Question": "Which of these animals is an amphibian?",
    "Option1": "Snake",
    "Option2": "Frog",
    "Option3": "Fish",
    "Option4": "Bird",
    "Answer": "Frog"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 5,
    "Question": "What is the largest living animal on Earth?",
    "Option1": "African Elephant",
    "Option2": "Blue Whale",
    "Option3": "Giant Squid",
    "Option4": "Giraffe",
    "Answer": "Blue Whale"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 6,
    "Question": "Which animal lays eggs and produces milk?",
    "Option1": "Kangaroo",
    "Option2": "Platypus",
    "Option3": "Bat",
    "Option4": "Dolphin",
    "Answer": "Platypus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 7,
    "Question": "What are animals that are active primarily during the night called?",
    "Option1": "Diurnal",
    "Option2": "Crepuscular",
    "Option3": "Nocturnal",
    "Option4": "Arboreal",
    "Answer": "Nocturnal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 8,
    "Question": "Which group of animals has an exoskeleton?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Mammals",
    "Option3": "Arthropods",
    "Option4": "Birds",
    "Answer": "Arthropods"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 9,
    "Question": "What is the process by which a caterpillar transforms into a butterfly?",
    "Option1": "Molting",
    "Option2": "Metamorphosis",
    "Option3": "Pupation",
    "Option4": "Hatching",
    "Answer": "Metamorphosis"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 10,
    "Question": "Which organ do fish use to breathe?",
    "Option1": "Lungs",
    "Option2": "Gills",
    "Option3": "Skin",
    "Option4": "Spiracles",
    "Answer": "Gills"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 11,
    "Question": "What type of animal is a spider?",
    "Option1": "Insect",
    "Option2": "Crustacean",
    "Option3": "Arachnid",
    "Option4": "Myriapod",
    "Answer": "Arachnid"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 12,
    "Question": "Which bird is known for its ability to mimic human speech?",
    "Option1": "Eagle",
    "Option2": "Penguin",
    "Option3": "Parrot",
    "Option4": "Ostrich",
    "Answer": "Parrot"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 13,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of lions?",
    "Option1": "Herd",
    "Option2": "Pack",
    "Option3": "Pride",
    "Option4": "Flock",
    "Answer": "Pride"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 14,
    "Question": "Which animal is famous for its long neck?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Giraffe",
    "Option3": "Rhino",
    "Option4": "Zebra",
    "Answer": "Giraffe"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 15,
    "Question": "What type of blood do mammals have?",
    "Option1": "Cold-blooded",
    "Option2": "Warm-blooded",
    "Option3": "Variable-blooded",
    "Option4": "No blood",
    "Answer": "Warm-blooded"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 16,
    "Question": "Which marine mammal uses echolocation to navigate and hunt?",
    "Option1": "Seal",
    "Option2": "Dolphin",
    "Option3": "Manatee",
    "Option4": "Walrus",
    "Answer": "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 17,
    "Question": "What is the protective outer covering of a turtle called?",
    "Option1": "Shell",
    "Option2": "Scales",
    "Option3": "Skin",
    "Option4": "Carapace",
    "Answer": "Carapace"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 18,
    "Question": "Which animal can change its color to blend with its surroundings?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Chameleon",
    "Option3": "Bear",
    "Option4": "Rabbit",
    "Answer": "Chameleon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 19,
    "Question": "What are baby kangaroos called?",
    "Option1": "Cubs",
    "Option2": "Pups",
    "Option3": "Joeys",
    "Option4": "Chicks",
    "Answer": "Joeys"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 20,
    "Question": "Which continent are penguins native to?",
    "Option1": "Africa",
    "Option2": "Asia",
    "Option3": "Antarctica",
    "Option4": "South America",
    "Answer": "Antarctica"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 21,
    "Question": "What is the main diet of a panda?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Bamboo",
    "Option3": "Meat",
    "Option4": "Fruits",
    "Answer": "Bamboo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 22,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for building elaborate dams?",
    "Option1": "Otter",
    "Option2": "Beaver",
    "Option3": "Muskrat",
    "Option4": "Mink",
    "Answer": "Beaver"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 23,
    "Question": "What is a group of fish called?",
    "Option1": "Colony",
    "Option2": "Swarm",
    "Option3": "School",
    "Option4": "Gaggle",
    "Answer": "School"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 24,
    "Question": "Which large cat is known for its distinctive stripes?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Leopard",
    "Option3": "Tiger",
    "Option4": "Cheetah",
    "Answer": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "question_no. 25": "What type of animal is a bat?",
    "Option1": "Bird",
    "Option2": "Insect",
    "Option3": "Mammal",
    "Option4": "Reptile",
    "Answer": "Mammal"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 26,
    "Question": "Which animal undergoes hibernation during winter?",
    "Option1": "Deer",
    "Option2": "Bear",
    "Option3": "Wolf",
    "Option4": "Fox",
    "Answer": "Bear"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 27,
    "Question": "What is the primary food source for baleen whales?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Seals",
    "Option3": "Krill",
    "Option4": "Sharks",
    "Answer": "Krill"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 28,
    "Question": "Which reptile is known for having a venomous bite and no legs?",
    "Option1": "Lizard",
    "Option2": "Turtle",
    "Option3": "Snake",
    "Option4": "Crocodile",
    "Answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 29,
    "Question": "What is the unique ability of a gecko's feet?",
    "Option1": "Flying",
    "Option2": "Walking on water",
    "Option3": "Clinging to almost any surface",
    "Option4": "Changing color",
    "Answer": "Clinging to almost any surface"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 30,
    "Question": "Which insect is known for producing honey?",
    "Option1": "Ant",
    "Option2": "Bee",
    "Option3": "Wasp",
    "Option4": "Fly",
    "Answer": "Bee"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 31,
    "Question": "What is the scientific name for humans?",
    "Option1": "Pan troglodytes",
    "Option2": "Gorilla gorilla",
    "Option3": "Homo sapiens",
    "Option4": "Pongo pygmaeus",
    "Answer": "Homo sapiens"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 32,
    "Question": "Which animal is characterized by its long, muscular prehensile tail?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Kangaroo",
    "Option3": "Monkey",
    "Option4": "Bear",
    "Answer": "Monkey"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 33,
    "Question": "What is the process of shedding an old skin or outer layer to make way for a new one, as done by reptiles and insects?",
    "Option1": "Hibernation",
    "Option2": "Estivation",
    "Option3": "Molting",
    "Option4": "Metamorphosis",
    "Answer": "Molting"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 34,
    "Question": "Which bird is known for its nocturnal hunting and excellent eyesight?",
    "Option1": "Eagle",
    "Option2": "Owl",
    "Option3": "Falcon",
    "Option4": "Hummingbird",
    "Answer": "Owl"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 35,
    "Question": "What is the fastest land animal?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Gazelle",
    "Option3": "Cheetah",
    "Option4": "Horse",
    "Answer": "Cheetah"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 36,
    "Question": "Which animal is a marsupial and native to Australia?",
    "Option1": "Tiger",
    "Option2": "Bear",
    "Option3": "Kangaroo",
    "Option4": "Wolf",
    "Answer": "Kangaroo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 37,
    "Question": "What is the largest living bird by wingspan?",
    "Option1": "Ostrich",
    "Option2": "Albatross",
    "Option3": "Eagle",
    "Option4": "Condor",
    "Answer": "Albatross"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 38,
    "Question": "Which animal uses camouflage as its primary defense mechanism?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Zebra",
    "Option3": "Octopus",
    "Option4": "Lion",
    "Answer": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 39,
    "Question": "What is the name for a young goat?",
    "Option1": "Calf",
    "Option2": "Kid",
    "Option3": "Lamb",
    "Option4": "Foal",
    "Answer": "Kid"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 40,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having feathers?",
    "Option1": "Reptiles",
    "Option2": "Mammals",
    "Option3": "Birds",
    "Option4": "Amphibians",
    "Answer": "Birds"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 41,
    "Question": "What is the longest living animal?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Greenland Shark",
    "Option3": "Giant Tortoise",
    "Option4": "Bowhead Whale",
    "Answer": "Greenland Shark"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 42,
    "Question": "Which animal builds a nest made of mud and sticks?",
    "Option1": "Spider",
    "Option2": "Termite",
    "Option3": "Beaver",
    "Option4": "Robin",
    "Answer": "Robin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 43,
    "Question": "What is the typical number of legs an insect has?",
    "Option1": "4",
    "Option2": "6",
    "Option3": "8",
    "Option4": "Many",
    "Answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 44,
    "Question": "Which of these animals is a primate?",
    "Option1": "Dog",
    "Option2": "Cat",
    "Option3": "Chimpanzee",
    "Option4": "Horse",
    "Answer": "Chimpanzee"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 45,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of owls?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Gaggle",
    "Option3": "Parliament",
    "Option4": "Covey",
    "Answer": "Parliament"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 46,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive black and white striped pattern?",
    "Option1": "Tiger",
    "Option2": "Zebra",
    "Option3": "Leopard",
    "Option4": "Jaguar",
    "Answer": "Zebra"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 47,
    "Question": "What is the term for animals that can live both on land and in water?",
    "Option1": "Marine",
    "Option2": "Terrestrial",
    "Option3": "Amphibious",
    "Option4": "Arboreal",
    "Answer": "Amphibious"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 48,
    "Question": "Which animal is capable of regenerating lost body parts, such as limbs or arms?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Starfish",
    "Option3": "Bird",
    "Option4": "Elephant",
    "Answer": "Starfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 49,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of a bird's feathers?",
    "Option1": "Breathing",
    "Option2": "Digestion",
    "Option3": "Flight and insulation",
    "Option4": "Hearing",
    "Answer": "Flight and insulation"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 50,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to produce venom for self-defense or hunting?",
    "Option1": "Rabbit",
    "Option2": "Deer",
    "Option3": "Scorpion",
    "Option4": "Cow",
    "Answer": "Scorpion"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 51,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of insects called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Entomology",
    "Option4": "Herpetology",
    "Answer": "Entomology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 52,
    "Question": "Which type of animal is a jellyfish?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Mollusk",
    "Option3": "Cnidarian",
    "Option4": "Crustacean",
    "Answer": "Cnidarian"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 53,
    "Question": "What do bats use to find their way in the dark?",
    "Option1": "Excellent night vision",
    "Option2": "Echolocation",
    "Option3": "Infrared sensing",
    "Option4": "Magnetic fields",
    "Answer": "Echolocation"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 54,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its elaborate courtship dances?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Peacock",
    "Option3": "Wolf",
    "Option4": "Giraffe",
    "Answer": "Peacock"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 55,
    "Question": "What is the largest living reptile?",
    "Option1": "Komodo Dragon",
    "Option2": "Green Anaconda",
    "Option3": "Saltwater Crocodile",
    "Option4": "Alligator",
    "Answer": "Saltwater Crocodile"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 56,
    "Question": "Which animal is a flightless bird native to New Zealand?",
    "Option1": "Ostrich",
    "Option2": "Emu",
    "Option3": "Kiwi",
    "Option4": "Penguin",
    "Answer": "Kiwi"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 57,
    "Question": "What is the primary food source of a koala?",
    "Option1": "Bamboo",
    "Option2": "Eucalyptus leaves",
    "Option3": "Insects",
    "Option4": "Fruits",
    "Answer": "Eucalyptus leaves"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 58,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its incredibly long tongue used to catch insects?",
    "Option1": "Frog",
    "Option2": "Chameleon",
    "Option3": "Anteater",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 59,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby deer?",
    "Option1": "Cub",
    "Option2": "Fawn",
    "Option3": "Pup",
    "Option4": "Calf",
    "Answer": "Fawn"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 60,
    "Question": "Which group of animals reproduces by laying eggs and typically has scales?",
    "Option1": "Mammals",
    "Option2": "Birds",
    "Option3": "Reptiles",
    "Option4": "Amphibians",
    "Answer": "Reptiles"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 61,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of fish?",
    "Option1": "Gaggle",
    "Option2": "Herd",
    "Option3": "School",
    "Option4": "Pack",
    "Answer": "School"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 62,
    "Question": "Which marine animal is known for its ability to mimic other marine creatures?",
    "Option1": "Great White Shark",
    "Option2": "Mimic Octopus",
    "Option3": "Blue Whale",
    "Option4": "Seahorse",
    "Answer": "Mimic Octopus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 63,
    "Question": "What is the only mammal capable of true sustained flight?",
    "Option1": "Squirrel",
    "Option2": "Flying Lemur",
    "Option3": "Bat",
    "Option4": "Sugar Glider",
    "Answer": "Bat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 64,
    "Question": "Which animal has the largest brain among all land animals?",
    "Option1": "Human",
    "Option2": "Elephant",
    "Option3": "Whale",
    "Option4": "Dolphin",
    "Answer": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 65,
    "Question": "What is the term for an animal that obtains its body heat from external sources?",
    "Option1": "Endotherm",
    "Option2": "Ectotherm",
    "Option3": "Homeotherm",
    "Option4": "Poikilotherm",
    "Answer": "Ectotherm"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 66,
    "Question": "Which of these animals is a monotreme?",
    "Option1": "Kangaroo",
    "Option2": "Platypus",
    "Option3": "Bear",
    "Option4": "Whale",
    "Answer": "Platypus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 67,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of wolves?",
    "Option1": "Herd",
    "Option2": "Pack",
    "Option3": "Flock",
    "Option4": "Colony",
    "Answer": "Pack"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 68,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to survive for long periods without water, thanks to its humps?",
    "Option1": "Camel",
    "Option2": "Zebra",
    "Option3": "Giraffe",
    "Option4": "Antelope",
    "Answer": "Camel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 69,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of birds called?",
    "Option1": "Entomology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Ornithology",
    "Option4": "Herpetology",
    "Answer": "Ornithology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 70,
    "Question": "Which animal uses its tusks primarily for digging for food and self-defense?",
    "Option1": "Elephant",
    "Option2": "Walrus",
    "Option3": "Wild Boar",
    "Option4": "Narwhal",
    "Answer": "Wild Boar"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 71,
    "Question": "What is the term for animals that eat both plants and animals?",
    "Option1": "Herbivore",
    "Option2": "Carnivore",
    "Option3": "Omnivore",
    "Option4": "Detritivore",
    "Answer": "Omnivore"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 72,
    "Question": "Which of these animals is a cold-blooded vertebrate with dry, scaly skin?",
    "Option1": "Frog",
    "Option2": "Salmon",
    "Option3": "Lizard",
    "Option4": "Bat",
    "Answer": "Lizard"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 73,
    "Question": "What is the largest land animal?",
    "Option1": "Polar Bear",
    "Option2": "Asian Elephant",
    "Option3": "African Bush Elephant",
    "Option4": "Giraffe",
    "Answer": "African Bush Elephant"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 74,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to spin silk for webs?",
    "Option1": "Ant",
    "Option2": "Bee",
    "Option3": "Spider",
    "Option4": "Butterfly",
    "Answer": "Spider"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 75,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of geese?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Herd",
    "Option3": "Gaggle",
    "Option4": "Swarm",
    "Answer": "Gaggle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 76,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its black and white fur and being the national animal of China?",
    "Option1": "Polar Bear",
    "Option2": "Giant Panda",
    "Option3": "Penguin",
    "Option4": "Orca",
    "Answer": "Giant Panda"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 77,
    "Question": "What type of animal is a seahorse?",
    "Option1": "Crustacean",
    "Option2": "Fish",
    "Option3": "Mollusk",
    "Option4": "Mammal",
    "Answer": "Fish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 78,
    "Question": "Which animal has the strongest bite force among living animals?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Hyena",
    "Option3": "Saltwater Crocodile",
    "Option4": "Great White Shark",
    "Answer": "Saltwater Crocodile"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 79,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby pig?",
    "Option1": "Calf",
    "Option2": "Lamb",
    "Option3": "Piglet",
    "Option4": "Chick",
    "Answer": "Piglet"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 80,
    "Question": "Which group of animals is characterized by metamorphosis and living in water as larvae and on land as adults?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Reptiles",
    "Option3": "Amphibians",
    "Option4": "Birds",
    "Answer": "Amphibians"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 81,
    "Question": "What is the longest animal in the world?",
    "Option1": "Blue Whale",
    "Option2": "Lion's Mane Jellyfish",
    "Option3": "Green Anaconda",
    "Option4": "Giant Squid",
    "Answer": "Lion's Mane Jellyfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 82,
    "Question": "Which bird is known for its ability to hover in mid-air?",
    "Option1": "Eagle",
    "Option2": "Hummingbird",
    "Option3": "Ostrich",
    "Option4": "Penguin",
    "Answer": "Hummingbird"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 83,
    "Question": "What is the primary characteristic of mammals that distinguishes them from other animals?",
    "Option1": "Laying eggs",
    "Option2": "Having scales",
    "Option3": "Producing milk to feed their young",
    "Option4": "Being cold-blooded",
    "Answer": "Producing milk to feed their young"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 84,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to fly backwards?",
    "Option1": "Eagle",
    "Option2": "Hummingbird",
    "Option3": "Pigeon",
    "Option4": "Sparrow",
    "Answer": "Hummingbird"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 85,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of fish called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Herpetology",
    "Option4": "Entomology",
    "Answer": "Ichthyology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 86,
    "Question": "Which animal undergoes estivation, a state of dormancy, during hot or dry periods?",
    "Option1": "Bear",
    "Option2": "African Lungfish",
    "Option3": "Bat",
    "Option4": "Squirrel",
    "Answer": "African Lungfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 87,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of crows?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Murder",
    "Option3": "Gaggle",
    "Option4": "School",
    "Answer": "Murder"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 88,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its venomous 'sting' and segmented body?",
    "Option1": "Spider",
    "Option2": "Scorpion",
    "Option3": "Centipede",
    "Option4": "Millipede",
    "Answer": "Scorpion"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 89,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby whale?",
    "Option1": "Pup",
    "Option2": "Calf",
    "Option3": "Cub",
    "Option4": "Kit",
    "Answer": "Calf"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 90,
    "Question": "Which group of animals typically undergoes complete metamorphosis, including a larval and pupal stage?",
    "Option1": "Spiders",
    "Option2": "Insects (like butterflies and beetles)",
    "Option3": "Fish",
    "Option4": "Reptiles",
    "Answer": "Insects (like butterflies and beetles)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 91,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of reptiles and amphibians called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Herpetology",
    "Option4": "Entomology",
    "Answer": "Herpetology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 92,
    "Question": "Which animal has a specialized pouch to carry its young?",
    "Option1": "Deer",
    "Option2": "Kangaroo",
    "Option3": "Bear",
    "Option4": "Wolf",
    "Answer": "Kangaroo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 93,
    "Question": "What is the primary food source for a vampire bat?",
    "Option1": "Fruits",
    "Option2": "Insects",
    "Option3": "Blood",
    "Option4": "Nectar",
    "Answer": "Blood"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 94,
    "Question": "Which bird is known for its distinctive long, pink legs and curved bill?",
    "Option1": "Swan",
    "Option2": "Flamingo",
    "Option3": "Pelican",
    "Option4": "Duck",
    "Answer": "Flamingo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 95,
    "Question": "What is the fastest marine animal?",
    "Option1": "Dolphin",
    "Option2": "Sailfish",
    "Option3": "Shark",
    "Option4": "Orca",
    "Answer": "Sailfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 96,
    "Question": "Which animal is an excellent swimmer and has a thick layer of blubber for insulation?",
    "Option1": "Deer",
    "Option2": "Polar Bear",
    "Option3": "Rabbit",
    "Option4": "Fox",
    "Answer": "Polar Bear"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 97,
    "Question": "What is the term for animals that reproduce by laying eggs?",
    "Option1": "Viviparous",
    "Option2": "Oviparous",
    "Option3": "Ovoviviparous",
    "Option4": "Parthenogenetic",
    "Answer": "Oviparous"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 98,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its impressive migration patterns across vast distances?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Monarch Butterfly",
    "Option3": "Elephant",
    "Option4": "Gorilla",
    "Answer": "Monarch Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 99,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby cow?",
    "Option1": "Foal",
    "Option2": "Cub",
    "Option3": "Calf",
    "Option4": "Kid",
    "Answer": "Calf"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 100,
    "Question": "Which group of animals has a cartilaginous skeleton instead of bone?",
    "Option1": "Bony Fish",
    "Option2": "Reptiles",
    "Option3": "Sharks and Rays",
    "Option4": "Mammals",
    "Answer": "Sharks and Rays"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 101,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of mammals called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Mammalogy",
    "Option4": "Herpetology",
    "Answer": "Mammalogy"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 102,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to deliver an electric shock?",
    "Option1": "Jellyfish",
    "Option2": "Electric Eel",
    "Option3": "Starfish",
    "Option4": "Octopus",
    "Answer": "Electric Eel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 103,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of highly venomous snakes?",
    "Option1": "Nest",
    "Option2": "Slither",
    "Option3": "Pit",
    "Option4": "Den",
    "Answer": "Pit"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 104,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to inflate its body as a defense mechanism?",
    "Option1": "Clownfish",
    "Option2": "Pufferfish",
    "Option3": "Anglerfish",
    "Option4": "Seahorse",
    "Answer": "Pufferfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 105,
    "Question": "What is the largest living bird that cannot fly?",
    "Option1": "Penguin",
    "Option2": "Kiwi",
    "Option3": "Ostrich",
    "Option4": "Emu",
    "Answer": "Ostrich"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 106,
    "Question": "Which animal has the unique ability to regrow its tail if it breaks off?",
    "Option1": "Snake",
    "Option2": "Lizard",
    "Option3": "Turtle",
    "Option4": "Crocodile",
    "Answer": "Lizard"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 107,
    "Question": "What is the primary characteristic of arthropods?",
    "Option1": "Internal skeleton",
    "Option2": "Soft body",
    "Option3": "Exoskeleton and jointed appendages",
    "Option4": "No symmetry",
    "Answer": "Exoskeleton and jointed appendages"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 108,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to change its skin texture to match its surroundings?",
    "Option1": "Chameleon",
    "Option2": "Octopus",
    "Option3": "Flounder",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 109,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby horse?",
    "Option1": "Colt",
    "Option2": "Filly",
    "Option3": "Foal",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 110,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are invertebrates with soft bodies, often protected by a shell?",
    "Option1": "Arthropods",
    "Option2": "Annelids",
    "Option3": "Mollusks",
    "Option4": "Cnidarians",
    "Answer": "Mollusks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 111,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of animal behavior called?",
    "Option1": "Ecology",
    "Option2": "Genetics",
    "Option3": "Ethology",
    "Option4": "Physiology",
    "Answer": "Ethology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 112,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its incredibly loud vocalizations, especially during mating season?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Howler Monkey",
    "Option3": "Elephant",
    "Option4": "Wolf",
    "Answer": "Howler Monkey"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 113,
    "Question": "What is the term for an animal that eats only meat?",
    "Option1": "Herbivore",
    "Option2": "Carnivore",
    "Option3": "Omnivore",
    "Option4": "Detritivore",
    "Answer": "Carnivore"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 114,
    "Question": "Which of these animals is a worm with a segmented body?",
    "Option1": "Tapeworm",
    "Option2": "Earthworm",
    "Option3": "Roundworm",
    "Option4": "Flatworm",
    "Answer": "Earthworm"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 115,
    "Question": "What is the largest land carnivore?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Grizzly Bear",
    "Option3": "Polar Bear",
    "Option4": "Tiger",
    "Answer": "Polar Bear"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 116,
    "Question": "Which animal builds large, intricate mounds that can be mistaken for small hills?",
    "Option1": "Ant",
    "Option2": "Termite",
    "Option3": "Beaver",
    "Option4": "Mole",
    "Answer": "Termite"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 117,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of fish?",
    "Option1": "Shool",
    "Option2": "School",
    "Option3": "Swarm",
    "Option4": "Colony",
    "Answer": "School"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 118,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique ability to walk upright on two legs while running?",
    "Option1": "Kangaroo",
    "Option2": "Bear",
    "Option3": "Chimpanzee",
    "Option4": "Gorilla",
    "Answer": "Kangaroo"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 119,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby dog?",
    "Option1": "Kitten",
    "Option2": "Pup",
    "Option3": "Calf",
    "Option4": "Chick",
    "Answer": "Pup"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 120,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having a hollow nerve cord, notochord, pharyngeal slits, and a post-anal tail at some stage of development?",
    "Option1": "Arthropods",
    "Option2": "Mollusks",
    "Option3": "Chordates",
    "Option4": "Cnidarians",
    "Answer": "Chordates"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 121,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of fish called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Herpetology",
    "Option4": "Entomology",
    "Answer": "Ichthyology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 122,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to spray a foul-smelling liquid as a defense mechanism?",
    "Option1": "Skunk",
    "Option2": "Fox",
    "Option3": "Badger",
    "Option4": "Raccoon",
    "Answer": "Skunk"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 123,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of kangaroos?",
    "Option1": "Herd",
    "Option2": "Mob",
    "Option3": "Pack",
    "Option4": "Flock",
    "Answer": "Mob"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 124,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique 'web' of connections in its brain, leading to exceptional intelligence?",
    "Option1": "Dolphin",
    "Option2": "Octopus",
    "Option3": "Crow",
    "Option4": "Elephant",
    "Answer": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 125,
    "Question": "What is the largest species of shark?",
    "Option1": "Great White Shark",
    "Option2": "Tiger Shark",
    "Option3": "Whale Shark",
    "Option4": "Hammerhead Shark",
    "Answer": "Whale Shark"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 126,
    "Question": "Which animal is a flightless bird known for its distinct three-toed feet?",
    "Option1": "Ostrich",
    "Option2": "Emu",
    "Option3": "Cassowary",
    "Option4": "Kiwi",
    "Answer": "Cassowary"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 127,
    "Question": "What is the primary food source of a sloth?",
    "Option1": "Insects",
    "Option2": "Leaves and buds",
    "Option3": "Fruits",
    "Option4": "Meat",
    "Answer": "Leaves and buds"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 128,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to mimic sounds from its environment, including human speech and car alarms?",
    "Option1": "Parrot",
    "Option2": "Mockingbird",
    "Option3": "Lyrebird",
    "Option4": "Myna Bird",
    "Answer": "Lyrebird"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 129,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby cat?",
    "Option1": "Pup",
    "Option2": "Cub",
    "Option3": "Kitten",
    "Option4": "Joey",
    "Answer": "Kitten"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 130,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having an internal skeleton, gills at some stage, and typically live in water?",
    "Option1": "Amphibians",
    "Option2": "Reptiles",
    "Option3": "Fish",
    "Option4": "Mammals",
    "Answer": "Fish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 131,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of mollusks called?",
    "Option1": "Malacology",
    "Option2": "Conchology",
    "Option3": "Both A and B",
    "Option4": "None of the above",
    "Answer": "Both A and B"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 132,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to 'play dead' when threatened?",
    "Option1": "Rabbit",
    "Option2": "Opossum",
    "Option3": "Squirrel",
    "Option4": "Mouse",
    "Answer": "Opossum"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 133,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of eagles?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Convocation",
    "Option3": "Parliament",
    "Option4": "School",
    "Answer": "Convocation"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 134,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive 'mane' around its neck?",
    "Option1": "Tiger",
    "Option2": "Lion",
    "Option3": "Leopard",
    "Option4": "Cheetah",
    "Answer": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 135,
    "Question": "What is the smallest mammal in the world?",
    "Option1": "Shrew",
    "Option2": "Bumblebee Bat",
    "Option3": "Mouse",
    "Option4": "Hamster",
    "Answer": "Bumblebee Bat"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 136,
    "Question": "Which animal has the unique ability to produce milk for its young, but also lays eggs?",
    "Option1": "Kangaroo",
    "Option2": "Echidna",
    "Option3": "Bat",
    "Option4": "Dolphin",
    "Answer": "Echidna"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 137,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of whiskers on animals like cats and seals?",
    "Option1": "Grooming",
    "Option2": "Balancing",
    "Option3": "Sensory perception and navigation",
    "Option4": "Defense",
    "Answer": "Sensory perception and navigation"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 138,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to spray ink as a defense mechanism?",
    "Option1": "Fish",
    "Option2": "Squid",
    "Option3": "Jellyfish",
    "Option4": "Starfish",
    "Answer": "Squid"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 139,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby bear?",
    "Option1": "Cub",
    "Option2": "Pup",
    "Option3": "Kit",
    "Option4": "Joey",
    "Answer": "Cub"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 140,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having a two-part shell and living in water?",
    "Option1": "Insects",
    "Option2": "Fish",
    "Option3": "Bivalves (e.g., clams, oysters)",
    "Option4": "Reptiles",
    "Answer": "Bivalves (e.g., clams, oysters)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 141,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of spiders and other arachnids called?",
    "Option1": "Entomology",
    "Option2": "Arachnology",
    "Option3": "Myriapodology",
    "Option4": "Carcinology",
    "Answer": "Arachnology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 142,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its incredible strength and ability to lift many times its own body weight?",
    "Option1": "Ant",
    "Option2": "Elephant",
    "Option3": "Gorilla",
    "Option4": "Bear",
    "Answer": "Ant"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 143,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of dolphins?",
    "Option1": "School",
    "Option2": "Pod",
    "Option3": "Herd",
    "Option4": "Flock",
    "Answer": "Pod"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 144,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive 'hoots' and being a symbol of wisdom?",
    "Option1": "Parrot",
    "Option2": "Owl",
    "Option3": "Eagle",
    "Option4": "Crow",
    "Answer": "Owl"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 145,
    "Question": "What is the fastest bird in the world?",
    "Option1": "Ostrich",
    "Option2": "Peregrine Falcon",
    "Option3": "Eagle",
    "Option4": "Hummingbird",
    "Answer": "Peregrine Falcon"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 146,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to change its sex during its lifetime?",
    "Option1": "Clownfish",
    "Option2": "Shark",
    "Option3": "Dolphin",
    "Option4": "Whale",
    "Answer": "Clownfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 147,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of gills in aquatic animals?",
    "Option1": "Feeding",
    "Option2": "Reproduction",
    "Option3": "Respiration (oxygen exchange)",
    "Option4": "Locomotion",
    "Answer": "Respiration (oxygen exchange)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 148,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its extremely long lifespan and slow movement?",
    "Option1": "Rabbit",
    "Option2": "Giant Tortoise",
    "Option3": "Lion",
    "Option4": "Elephant",
    "Answer": "Giant Tortoise"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 149,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby bird?",
    "Option1": "Pup",
    "Option2": "Cub",
    "Option3": "Chick",
    "Option4": "Fawn",
    "Answer": "Chick"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 150,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having radial symmetry and tube feet?",
    "Option1": "Mollusks",
    "Option2": "Arthropods",
    "Option3": "Echinoderms (e.g., starfish, sea urchins)",
    "Option4": "Annelids",
    "Answer": "Echinoderms (e.g., starfish, sea urchins)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 151,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of amphibians and reptiles called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Herpetology",
    "Option4": "Entomology",
    "Answer": "Herpetology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 152,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to detach its tail to escape predators?",
    "Option1": "Snake",
    "Option2": "Some Lizards",
    "Option3": "Turtle",
    "Option4": "Crocodile",
    "Answer": "Some Lizards"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 153,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of highly intelligent birds, like ravens?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Parliament",
    "Option3": "Unkindness",
    "Option4": "Murder",
    "Answer": "Unkindness"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 154,
    "Question": "Which animal has the largest eyes of any animal?",
    "Option1": "Giant Squid",
    "Option2": "Whale",
    "Option3": "Owl",
    "Option4": "Eagle",
    "Answer": "Giant Squid"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 155,
    "Question": "What is the largest land mammal?",
    "Option1": "African Elephant",
    "Option2": "Asian Elephant",
    "Option3": "White Rhinoceros",
    "Option4": "Hippopotamus",
    "Answer": "African Elephant"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 156,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to use tools?",
    "Option1": "Dog",
    "Option2": "Chimpanzee",
    "Option3": "Cat",
    "Option4": "Rabbit",
    "Answer": "Chimpanzee"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 157,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of a whale's blowhole?",
    "Option1": "Feeding",
    "Option2": "Breathing",
    "Option3": "Echolocation",
    "Option4": "Swimming",
    "Answer": "Breathing"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 158,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive 'roar' and being the 'king of the jungle' (though it lives on savannas)?",
    "Option1": "Tiger",
    "Option2": "Lion",
    "Option3": "Leopard",
    "Option4": "Cheetah",
    "Answer": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 159,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby rabbit?",
    "Option1": "Pup",
    "Option2": "Kit",
    "Option3": "Fawn",
    "Option4": "Cub",
    "Answer": "Kit"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 160,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are segmented worms?",
    "Option1": "Flatworms",
    "Option2": "Roundworms",
    "Option3": "Annelids (e.g., earthworms, leeches)",
    "Option4": "Nematodes",
    "Answer": "Annelids (e.g., earthworms, leeches)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 161,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of fish and their habitats called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Ichthyology",
    "Option3": "Limnology",
    "Option4": "Marine Biology",
    "Answer": "Ichthyology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 162,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to survive extreme cold temperatures due to its antifreeze proteins?",
    "Option1": "Penguin",
    "Option2": "Polar Bear",
    "Option3": "Arctic Cod",
    "Option4": "Walrus",
    "Answer": "Arctic Cod"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 163,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of fish?",
    "Option1": "School",
    "Option2": "Pod",
    "Option3": "Colony",
    "Option4": "Swarm",
    "Answer": "School"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 164,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive 'trunk' used for grasping, smelling, and breathing?",
    "Option1": "Giraffe",
    "Option2": "Rhinoceros",
    "Option3": "Elephant",
    "Option4": "Hippopotamus",
    "Answer": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 165,
    "Question": "What is the largest type of ape?",
    "Option1": "Chimpanzee",
    "Option2": "Orangutan",
    "Option3": "Gorilla",
    "Option4": "Bonobo",
    "Answer": "Gorilla"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 166,
    "Question": "Which animal is a flightless bird known for its distinctive long, strong legs and ability to run at high speeds?",
    "Option1": "Kiwi",
    "Option2": "Emu",
    "Option3": "Penguin",
    "Option4": "Ostrich",
    "Answer": "Ostrich"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 167,
    "Question": "What is the primary food source of a bat?",
    "Option1": "Fruits and nectar",
    "Option2": "Insects",
    "Option3": "Blood",
    "Option4": "All of the above (depending on the species)",
    "Answer": "All of the above (depending on the species)"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 168,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to change its skin color, texture, and pattern to blend perfectly with its environment?",
    "Option1": "Chameleon",
    "Option2": "Octopus",
    "Option3": "Cuttlefish",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 169,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby goat?",
    "Option1": "Kid",
    "Option2": "Lamb",
    "Option3": "Calf",
    "Option4": "Foal",
    "Answer": "Kid"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 170,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are jawless fish?",
    "Option1": "Sharks",
    "Option2": "Rays",
    "Option3": "Lampreys and Hagfish",
    "Option4": "Bony Fish",
    "Answer": "Lampreys and Hagfish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 171,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of worms (excluding insects) called?",
    "Option1": "Entomology",
    "Option2": "Helminthology",
    "Option3": "Arachnology",
    "Option4": "Malacology",
    "Answer": "Helminthology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 172,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique ability to curl into a ball when threatened?",
    "Option1": "Hedgehog",
    "Option2": "Armadillo",
    "Option3": "Pangolin",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 173,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of fish?",
    "Option1": "Shoal",
    "Option2": "School",
    "Option3": "Swarm",
    "Option4": "Pod",
    "Answer": "School"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 174,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its elaborate and colorful tail feathers used for display?",
    "Option1": "Eagle",
    "Option2": "Peacock",
    "Option3": "Pheasant",
    "Option4": "Turkey",
    "Answer": "Peacock"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 175,
    "Question": "What is the largest land predator?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Tiger",
    "Option3": "Polar Bear",
    "Option4": "Grizzly Bear",
    "Answer": "Polar Bear"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 176,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to build complex underwater structures for shelter and camouflage?",
    "Option1": "Coral",
    "Option2": "Beaver",
    "Option3": "Octopus",
    "Option4": "Spider Crab",
    "Answer": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 177,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of a shark's lateral line system?",
    "Option1": "Smelling prey",
    "Option2": "Detecting vibrations and pressure changes in water",
    "Option3": "Echolocation",
    "Option4": "Generating electric fields",
    "Answer": "Detecting vibrations and pressure changes in water"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 178,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive stripes and being a powerful, solitary hunter?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Tiger",
    "Option3": "Leopard",
    "Option4": "Cheetah",
    "Answer": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 179,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby sheep?",
    "Option1": "Kid",
    "Option2": "Lamb",
    "Option3": "Calf",
    "Option4": "Fawn",
    "Answer": "Lamb"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 180,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having an internal skeleton, scales, fins, and breathing through gills throughout their lives?",
    "Option1": "Amphibians",
    "Option2": "Reptiles",
    "Option3": "Fish",
    "Option4": "Mammals",
    "Answer": "Fish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 181,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of parasites called?",
    "Option1": "Virology",
    "Option2": "Bacteriology",
    "Option3": "Parasitology",
    "Option4": "Mycology",
    "Answer": "Parasitology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 182,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to 'walk' on water using surface tension?",
    "Option1": "Diving Beetle",
    "Option2": "Water Strider",
    "Option3": "Dragonfly",
    "Option4": "Mosquito",
    "Answer": "Water Strider"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 183,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of bears?",
    "Option1": "Pack",
    "Option2": "Sleuth or Sloth",
    "Option3": "Herd",
    "Option4": "Flock",
    "Answer": "Sleuth or Sloth"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 184,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its incredibly long, sticky tongue used to catch ants and termites?",
    "Option1": "Frog",
    "Option2": "Anteater",
    "Option3": "Chameleon",
    "Option4": "Lizard",
    "Answer": "Anteater"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 185,
    "Question": "What is the primary way birds communicate?",
    "Option1": "Through scent marking",
    "Option2": "Through complex vocalizations and displays",
    "Option3": "Through chemical signals",
    "Option4": "Through touch",
    "Answer": "Through complex vocalizations and displays"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 186,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its impressive ability to build intricate and symmetrical webs?",
    "Option1": "Ant",
    "Option2": "Spider",
    "Option3": "Silkworm",
    "Option4": "Caterpillar",
    "Answer": "Spider"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 187,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of a snake's Jacobson's organ?",
    "Option1": "Hearing",
    "Option2": "Smelling and tasting prey",
    "Option3": "Seeing in the dark",
    "Option4": "Detecting vibrations",
    "Answer": "Smelling and tasting prey"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 188,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its distinctive 'stripes' and being an excellent ambush predator?",
    "Option1": "Lion",
    "Option2": "Tiger",
    "Option3": "Leopard",
    "Option4": "Cheetah",
    "Answer": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 189,
    "Question": "What is the name for a baby goose?",
    "Option1": "Chick",
    "Option2": "Duckling",
    "Option3": "Gosling",
    "Option4": "Cygnets",
    "Answer": "Gosling"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 190,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by having a soft body and often a mantle that secretes a shell?",
    "Option1": "Arthropods",
    "Option2": "Annelids",
    "Option3": "Mollusks",
    "Option4": "Echinoderms",
    "Answer": "Mollusks"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 191,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of the classification of living organisms called?",
    "Option1": "Ecology",
    "Option2": "Physiology",
    "Option3": "Taxonomy",
    "Option4": "Anatomy",
    "Answer": "Taxonomy"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 192,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to change its skin color, texture, and pattern for rapid communication and display?",
    "Option1": "Chameleon",
    "Option2": "Octopus",
    "Option3": "Squid",
    "Option4": "Cuttlefish",
    "Answer": "Cuttlefish"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 193,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of snakes?",
    "Option1": "Slither",
    "Option2": "Pit",
    "Option3": "Den",
    "Option4": "Nest",
    "Answer": "Pit"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 194,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its incredibly long proboscis used to drink nectar from flowers?",
    "Option1": "Bee",
    "Option2": "Butterfly",
    "Option3": "Hummingbird",
    "Option4": "Mosquito",
    "Answer": "Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 195,
    "Question": "What is the primary function of a bird's beak?",
    "Option1": "Hearing",
    "Option2": "Feeding and grooming",
    "Option3": "Breathing",
    "Option4": "Flight",
    "Answer": "Feeding and grooming"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 196,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique ability to walk on the ceiling and walls?",
    "Option1": "Spider",
    "Option2": "Fly",
    "Option3": "Gecko",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "Gecko"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 197,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of animal development from fertilization to birth or hatching?",
    "Option1": "Genetics",
    "Option2": "Embryology",
    "Option3": "Anatomy",
    "Option4": "Physiology",
    "Answer": "Embryology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 198,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to generate light through bioluminescence?",
    "Option1": "Jellyfish",
    "Option2": "Firefly",
    "Option3": "Anglerfish",
    "Option4": "All of the above",
    "Answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 199,
    "Question": "What is the name for a young fish?",
    "Option1": "Fry",
    "Option2": "Tadpole",
    "Option3": "Fingerling",
    "Option4": "Both A and C",
    "Answer": "Both A and C"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 200,
    "Question": "Which group of animals are characterized by a segmented body, jointed legs, and an exoskeleton?",
    "Option1": "Mollusks",
    "Option2": "Annelids",
    "Option3": "Arthropods",
    "Option4": "Echinoderms",
    "Answer": "Arthropods"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 201,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of animal diseases called?",
    "Option1": "Pathology",
    "Option2": "Epidemiology",
    "Option3": "Veterinary medicine",
    "Option4": "Zoopathology",
    "Answer": "Zoopathology"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 202,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique ability to store fat and water in its humps?",
    "Option1": "Camel",
    "Option2": "Bison",
    "Option3": "Yak",
    "Option4": "Zebu",
    "Answer": "Camel"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 203,
    "Question": "What is the collective noun for a group of bats?",
    "Option1": "Flock",
    "Option2": "Colony",
    "Option3": "Swarm",
    "Option4": "Pack",
    "Answer": "Colony"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 204,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its unique ability to 'sing' complex songs underwater?",
    "Option1": "Dolphin",
    "Option2": "Humpback Whale",
    "Option3": "Seal",
    "Option4": "Orca",
    "Answer": "Humpback Whale"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 205,
    "Question": "What is the primary adaptation that allows birds to fly?",
    "Option1": "Strong legs",
    "Option2": "Hollow bones and feathers",
    "Option3": "Large brains",
    "Option4": "Thick fur",
    "Answer": "Hollow bones and feathers"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 206,
    "Question": "Which animal is known for its ability to produce pearls?",
    "Option1": "Crab",
    "Option2": "Oyster",
    "Option3": "Lobster",
    "Option4": "Starfish",
    "Answer": "Oyster"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 207,
    "Question": "What is the scientific study of insects called?",
    "Option1": "Ornithology",
    "Option2": "Entomology",
    "Option3": "Ichthyology",
    "Option4": "Herpetology",
    "Answer": "Entomology"
  }
]